<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DevOps on Dan Belmonte</title>
    <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/categories/devops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DevOps on Dan Belmonte</description>
    <image>
      <title>Dan Belmonte</title>
      <url>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</url>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:37:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dangaiden.github.io/categories/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My CKS experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/cks-exam-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/cks-exam-experience/</guid>
      <description>It was about time&amp;hellip; TL;DR A couple of months ago I&amp;rsquo;ve taken the CKS exam last week and I have passed it. It was about time to make a post about it which can be helpful to others.
After studying for some weeks of studying (in fact, I scheduled the exam a week before the exam was expiring) and two attempts, I got the pass, the first was just to be safe as it was going to expire but the second one, let me 2 additional weeks to nail a couple of things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My CKAD experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/ckad-exam-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/ckad-exam-experience/</guid>
      <description>Another Kubernetes exam: CKAD TL;DR I passed the CKAD exam a couple of weeks ago. As I already expected, it was easier than the CKA. Most of the resources to be used are the same than the CKA.
How much do I study for this one? Well, I already have experience with Kubernetes, took the CKA 3 weeks ago so I just took twice the killer.sh test and It was enough but your mileage may vary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github Actions Concurrency</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/ghactions-concurrency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/ghactions-concurrency/</guid>
      <description>GitHub Actions concurrency </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My CKA experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/cka-exam-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/cka-exam-experience/</guid>
      <description>It was about time&amp;hellip; TL;DR Last week I&amp;rsquo;ve taken the CKA exam last week and I have passed it! You can read the rest of the post for more insights and resources.
I have been studying for 2-3 weeks but I wanted to share what I have used to study although I already have experience with Kubernetes so your mileage may vary.
Anyway, I really like the practice exams as they really test you but practice and understand things instead of memorizing questions from a test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-400 exam notes</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2021-06-08-az-400-exam-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2021-06-08-az-400-exam-notes/</guid>
      <description>Some months missing between my last update!
I must say I have been quite busy with the new position and the massive change that has impacted my previous knowledge but overall, I am pretty happy with it!
Therefore, let&amp;rsquo;s move to the point! So I just want to share some notes of the AZ-400 exam which I recently passed and I hope that can be useful to someone.
Certification details This exam (AZ-400) is the second one of the path to the specific «Microsoft Certified: DevOps Engineer Expert» certification:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the applications’ future «containe(r)d»?</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-10-31-applications-future-containerd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 20:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-10-31-applications-future-containerd/</guid>
      <description>Well, I’ll be lying if I haven’t heard of containers in the past years although I used them barely at my job (solutions engineer) shouldn’t I consider them more every time to replace the applications where my customers have their servers?
Like many people that work as sysadmin these days, they are used to work with virtualization, in particular Virtual Machines (VMs), customers still using them (and it will continue) to deploy their applications in an OS which delivers great benefits against the legacy approach of the Baremetal (Mainframe) era.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finishing a Computer Engineering degree with DevOps stuff</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-10-19-finishing-a-computer-engineering-degree-with-devops-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 12:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-10-19-finishing-a-computer-engineering-degree-with-devops-stuff/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been more than one month since I published something here but I&amp;rsquo;ve been changing quite a lot my focus learning and I changed now from CCNA to DevOps things.
TL;DR I will be building an automated CI/CD pipeline for my final assignment focusing on tools installed and configured on-premise although there will be cloud services like the front-end.
Also, I forgot to mention that last month I started the last semester of my Computer Engineering degree that I started back in 2014 (oh my!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
