<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>vcap on Dan Belmonte</title>
    <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/tags/vcap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vcap on Dan Belmonte</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</url>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 22:47:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dangaiden.github.io/tags/vcap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>VCAP-DCV Design exam notes</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-31-vcap-dcv-design-exam-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 22:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-31-vcap-dcv-design-exam-notes/</guid>
      <description>As the VCAP-DCV Design 2020 certification is going to be released (but the 3V0-624 exam is not scheduled to be retired yet) on Jan 1, 2020.
Recently I made another post about my experience with this exam where I failed, check it here.
For your information, at the moment the 3V0-624 is the current exam code for the VCAP-DCV 6.5 Design certification (Also named VCAP-DCV Design 2019), always check the code for the exam no matter which is the certification name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCAP6.5-DCV Design failed exam experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-25-vcap6-5-dcv-design-failed-exam-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 21:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-25-vcap6-5-dcv-design-failed-exam-experience/</guid>
      <description>Recently I took the 3V0-624 exam (a.k.a. VMware Certified Advanced Professional 6.5 – Data Center Virtualization Design Exam) and I failed (266/500).
I took it on September, 4th (a month and a half ago) and as I was on holiday and now preparing things for VMworld Europe I won’t be able to study after the event.
I recognize, I study a bit in a rush. In just one month for someone who is daily tasks aren’t about architecture, it can be hard (or not).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCAP6-DCV Deploy exam experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-10-19-vcap6-dcv-deploy-exam-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 07:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-10-19-vcap6-dcv-deploy-exam-experience/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I am going to talk about my VCAP6-DCV Deploy exam experience.
I thought about making a huge post about the VCAP6-DCV experience (resources, notes, etc.) but, I don’t want to overwhelm you know. Hence, I am going to make another post for that, hence this post will be shorter and more readable.
1st attempt (Java error at the beginning) At September, 21st I sat down to take my first attempt in a VCAP exam.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
