<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>certification on Dan Belmonte</title>
    <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/tags/certification/</link>
    <description>Recent content in certification on Dan Belmonte</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</url>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 11:37:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dangaiden.github.io/tags/certification/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My CKA experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/cka-exam-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/cka-exam-experience/</guid>
      <description>My CKA experience TL;DR Last week I&amp;rsquo;ve taken the CKA exam and I have passed it!
I have been studying for 2-3 weeks but I wanted to share what I have used to study although I already have experience with Kubernetes so your millage may vary.
Anyway, I really like the practice exams as they really test you but practicing and understaing things instead of memorizing questions from a test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes the hard way but on-prem - part 1 (Discontinued)</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/kubernetes-the-hard-way-but-on-prem-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 11:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/kubernetes-the-hard-way-but-on-prem-part-1/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER  I decided to not continue with this due to the huge implications that will be to redo everything not in the cloud. Basically, a lot of time should be invested and I miscalculated it by too much. Therefore, this will be probably the first and only post about these series.
 Context In order to practice for the CKA exam, it is recommended to perform the famous Kubernetes The Hard Way by Kelsey Hightower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-400 exam notes</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2021-06-08-az-400-exam-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2021-06-08-az-400-exam-notes/</guid>
      <description>Some months missing between my last update!
I must say I have been quite busy with the new position and the massive change that has impacted my previous knowledge but overall, I am pretty happy with it!
Therefore, let&amp;rsquo;s move to the point! So I just want to share some notes of the AZ-400 exam which I recently passed and I hope that can be useful to someone.
Certification details This exam (AZ-400) is the second one of the path to the specific «Microsoft Certified: DevOps Engineer Expert» certification:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCAP-DCV Design exam notes</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-31-vcap-dcv-design-exam-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 22:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-31-vcap-dcv-design-exam-notes/</guid>
      <description>As the VCAP-DCV Design 2020 certification is going to be released (but the 3V0-624 exam is not scheduled to be retired yet) on Jan 1, 2020.
Recently I made another post about my experience with this exam where I failed, check it here.
For your information, at the moment the 3V0-624 is the current exam code for the VCAP-DCV 6.5 Design certification (Also named VCAP-DCV Design 2019), always check the code for the exam no matter which is the certification name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCAP6.5-DCV Design failed exam experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-25-vcap6-5-dcv-design-failed-exam-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 21:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-25-vcap6-5-dcv-design-failed-exam-experience/</guid>
      <description>Recently I took the 3V0-624 exam (a.k.a. VMware Certified Advanced Professional 6.5 – Data Center Virtualization Design Exam) and I failed (266/500).
I took it on September, 4th (a month and a half ago) and as I was on holiday and now preparing things for VMworld Europe I won’t be able to study after the event.
I recognize, I study a bit in a rush. In just one month for someone who is daily tasks aren’t about architecture, it can be hard (or not).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exam 70-743, Upgrading MCSA Windows Server 2016 experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/?p=704/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 11:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/?p=704/</guid>
      <description>I will explain quickly my experience regarding the Exam 70-743, Upgrading Your Skills to MCSA: Windows Server 2016 exam from Microsoft I took last April.
It’s been a while since I took an exam from Microsoft (the latestwas in 2013 I think) where you probably know that these kind of exams are multiple-choice or single-choice.
Through my career, I saw a lot of people cheating with these exams by memorizing the questions you can find on the internet and finishing it in just 20 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCAP6-DCV Deploy exam experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-10-19-vcap6-dcv-deploy-exam-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 07:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-10-19-vcap6-dcv-deploy-exam-experience/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I am going to talk about my VCAP6-DCV Deploy exam experience.
I thought about making a huge post about the VCAP6-DCV experience (resources, notes, etc.) but, I don’t want to overwhelm you know. Hence, I am going to make another post for that, hence this post will be shorter and more readable.
1st attempt (Java error at the beginning) At September, 21st I sat down to take my first attempt in a VCAP exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCP6-DCV achieved!</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2017-09-03-vcp6-dcv-achieved/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 16:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2017-09-03-vcp6-dcv-achieved/</guid>
      <description>I am going to start talking about the exam VCP6-DCV from VMware. The main resource you should use is the VMware site: http://bit.ly/1PLshWR
There you can check a path to achieve VCP6-DCV (there is a newer version VCP6.5-DCV). I took path 1, as I wasn’t certified.

Later, I took one official training course, VMware vSphere: Install, Configure, Manage [V6].
Next, I passed the vSphere 6 Foundations Exam (2V0-620) months ago and finally I did VMware Certified Professional 6 – Data Center Virtualization Exam (2V0-621).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes the hard way but on-prem - part 2</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/kubernetes-the-hard-way-but-on-prem-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/kubernetes-the-hard-way-but-on-prem-part2/</guid>
      <description>Context Let&amp;rsquo;s continue with the guide, in this part 2.
This is based in: https://github.com/kelseyhightower/kubernetes-the-hard-way/blob/master/docs/03-compute-resources.md
Kubernetes Controllers We will be using the following CIDR 192.168.1.0/24 for node within the cluster:
 Somred1: 192.168.1.50/24 Somred2: 192.168.1.51/24 Somred3: 192.168.1.52/24  Kubernetes Workers This nodes will act as the Kubernetes workers nodes which will host the pods, we need to have 2 NICs for each node.
One NIC will be the one used before to communicate with the other nodes: 192.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
