<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>clones on IT Gaiden</title>
    <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/tags/clones/</link>
    <description>Recent content in clones on IT Gaiden</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 10:25:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dangaiden.github.io/tags/clones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cloning virtual machines in vSphere series – Part 3: Linked Clones</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/?p=593/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 10:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/?p=593/</guid>
      <description>Let’s start with part 3 in the cloning virtual machines in vSphereseries, I am going to talk about another type of clones, linked clones! All articles regarding cloning virtual machines in vSphereseries:As said in previous articles, this series is only focused on VMware vSphere hence, VMware Horizon View is not contemplated (Linked clones are commonly usedin that product). What is a linked clone? What can you see here?
In the previous image, you can see 3 different characters but they share something in common…the actor!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloning virtual machines in vSphere series – Part 2: Full clone</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/?p=591/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/?p=591/</guid>
      <description>Continuing with the cloning virtual machines in vSphereseries, today I am going to write about the full clone, how it works and some useful information about it.So, let’s talk about clones… but just full clones.How does it work? As you probably know a full clone is an exact copy of a source VM, meaning that, everything from the parent VM is copied (VM settings, disks, files, etc.).This action can be performed if the parent VM is powered off or powered onand, if it has snapshots it will consolidate them once the clone is done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloning virtual machines in vSphere series – Part 1: Types of clone</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/?p=577/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 10:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/?p=577/</guid>
      <description>Most of you already know how to clone virtual machines within vSphere, and I mean cloning from the vSphere Web client within vCenter but, beyond that, there are other types of clones you can use in vCenter like, Linked Clones or Instant Clones (aka Project Fargo/VMfork)Due to the large content that can be discussed about each clone’s type, I decided to make a short series of poststalking about cloning VMs! Types of clone Here I will summarize each type of clone that exists in vSphere, some of them are used in different products or interfaces but in the end, all of them are accessible through PowerCLI.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
