<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>devops on Dan Belmonte</title>
    <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/tags/devops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in devops on Dan Belmonte</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</url>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 11:37:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dangaiden.github.io/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Github Actions Concurrency</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/ghactions-concurrency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/ghactions-concurrency/</guid>
      <description>GitHub Actions concurrency </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My CKA experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/cka-exam-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/cka-exam-experience/</guid>
      <description>It was about time&amp;hellip;  TL;DR Last week I&amp;rsquo;ve taken the CKA exam last week and I have passed it! You can read the rest of the post for more insights and resources.
 I have been studying for 2-3 weeks but I wanted to share what I have used to study although I already have experience with Kubernetes so your mileage may vary.
Anyway, I really like the practice exams as they really test you but practice and understand things instead of memorizing questions from a test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-400 exam notes</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2021-06-08-az-400-exam-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2021-06-08-az-400-exam-notes/</guid>
      <description>Some months missing between my last update!
I must say I have been quite busy with the new position and the massive change that has impacted my previous knowledge but overall, I am pretty happy with it!
Therefore, let&amp;rsquo;s move to the point! So I just want to share some notes of the AZ-400 exam which I recently passed and I hope that can be useful to someone.
Certification details This exam (AZ-400) is the second one of the path to the specific «Microsoft Certified: DevOps Engineer Expert» certification:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finishing a Computer Engineering degree with DevOps stuff</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-10-19-finishing-a-computer-engineering-degree-with-devops-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 12:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-10-19-finishing-a-computer-engineering-degree-with-devops-stuff/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been more than one month since I published something here but I&amp;rsquo;ve been changing quite a lot my focus learning and I changed now from CCNA to DevOps things.
 TL;DR I will be building an automated CI/CD pipeline for my final assignment focusing on tools installed and configured on-premise although there will be cloud services like the front-end.
 Also, I forgot to mention that last month I started the last semester of my Computer Engineering degree that I started back in 2014 (oh my!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
