<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>barcelona on Dan Belmonte</title>
    <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/tags/barcelona/</link>
    <description>Recent content in barcelona on Dan Belmonte</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</url>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 09:54:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dangaiden.github.io/tags/barcelona/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>VMworld 2019 Europe local guide</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-14-vmworld-2019-europe-local-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 09:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-14-vmworld-2019-europe-local-guide/</guid>
      <description>VMworld 2019 Europe is almost here! And I made a local guide with tips about transport, restaurants, places to go, etc. to ensure you can enjoy more your experience in VMworld.
General information This event will take place from the 4th (Monday) to 7th (Thursday) of November at Fira Gran Via in Barcelona, Spain.
VMworld is always an amazing opportunity to learn from all the events that will happen there like the Hands-on Lab, Breakout sessions, General sessions, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience at VMworld 2018 Europe – Day 2</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-12-13-vmworld-18-eu-day2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 09:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-12-13-vmworld-18-eu-day2/</guid>
      <description>Today I am going to explain from my personal experience, the Day 2 at VMworld 2018 Europe, lots of networking, some technical sessions, events and the Solutions Exchange.

Before moving forward, I forgot to mention that I met in my first day a nice guy, Daniel Paluszek @dpaluszek, we had a great conversation and he should be known as the vCloud Director guy ;).
vBreakfast If you don’t what is, check it here: http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience at VMworld 2018 Europe – Day 1</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-11-19-vmworld-18-eu-day1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-11-19-vmworld-18-eu-day1/</guid>
      <description>Let me talk to you about my experience on my first VMworld! This is a personal experience I want to share about Day 1 at VMworld 2018 Europe.
Introduction I live in Barcelona so, I am fortunate that I don’t need to travel to go to the VMworld Europe. The only thing is to commute by train between home and Fira Barcelona (where VMworld is established). 
It was Monday, November 5th, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
