<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Education on Dan Belmonte</title>
    <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/categories/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Education on Dan Belmonte</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</url>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 11:37:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dangaiden.github.io/categories/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Github Actions Concurrency</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/ghactions-concurrency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/ghactions-concurrency/</guid>
      <description>GitHub Actions concurrency </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My CKA experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/cka-exam-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/cka-exam-experience/</guid>
      <description>It was about time&amp;hellip;  TL;DR Last week I&amp;rsquo;ve taken the CKA exam last week and I have passed it! You can read the rest of the post for more insights and resources.
 I have been studying for 2-3 weeks but I wanted to share what I have used to study although I already have experience with Kubernetes so your mileage may vary.
Anyway, I really like the practice exams as they really test you but practice and understand things instead of memorizing questions from a test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-400 exam notes</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2021-06-08-az-400-exam-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2021-06-08-az-400-exam-notes/</guid>
      <description>Some months missing between my last update!
I must say I have been quite busy with the new position and the massive change that has impacted my previous knowledge but overall, I am pretty happy with it!
Therefore, let&amp;rsquo;s move to the point! So I just want to share some notes of the AZ-400 exam which I recently passed and I hope that can be useful to someone.
Certification details This exam (AZ-400) is the second one of the path to the specific «Microsoft Certified: DevOps Engineer Expert» certification:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 review</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-12-31-2019-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-12-31-2019-review/</guid>
      <description>I haven’t thought of doing this kind of review but reading some of them through the internet, it motivated me to do it.
Also by submitting to programs like vExpert from VMware, made me realize that I did many things this year that I forgot and were amazing.
2019 Timeline  January: Going to the gym to get healthier knees and finished exams from the university with good scores. Semester ends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCAP-DCV Design exam notes</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-31-vcap-dcv-design-exam-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 22:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-31-vcap-dcv-design-exam-notes/</guid>
      <description>As the VCAP-DCV Design 2020 certification is going to be released (but the 3V0-624 exam is not scheduled to be retired yet) on Jan 1, 2020.
Recently I made another post about my experience with this exam where I failed, check it here.
For your information, at the moment the 3V0-624 is the current exam code for the VCAP-DCV 6.5 Design certification (Also named VCAP-DCV Design 2019), always check the code for the exam no matter which is the certification name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCAP6.5-DCV Design failed exam experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-25-vcap6-5-dcv-design-failed-exam-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 21:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-25-vcap6-5-dcv-design-failed-exam-experience/</guid>
      <description>Recently I took the 3V0-624 exam (a.k.a. VMware Certified Advanced Professional 6.5 – Data Center Virtualization Design Exam) and I failed (266/500).
I took it on September, 4th (a month and a half ago) and as I was on holiday and now preparing things for VMworld Europe I won’t be able to study after the event.
I recognize, I study a bit in a rush. In just one month for someone who is daily tasks aren’t about architecture, it can be hard (or not).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exam 70-743, Upgrading MCSA Windows Server 2016 experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/?p=704/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 11:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/?p=704/</guid>
      <description>I will explain quickly my experience regarding the Exam 70-743, Upgrading Your Skills to MCSA: Windows Server 2016 exam from Microsoft I took last April.
It’s been a while since I took an exam from Microsoft (the latestwas in 2013 I think) where you probably know that these kind of exams are multiple-choice or single-choice.
Through my career, I saw a lot of people cheating with these exams by memorizing the questions you can find on the internet and finishing it in just 20 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT skills: Which gap to fill?</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-01-31-it-skills-which-gap-to-fill/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 09:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-01-31-it-skills-which-gap-to-fill/</guid>
      <description>Regarding this nice article, I read while ago from Eric Shanks: https://theithollow.com/2018/03/26/fill-skills-tank/.
I decided to write about it as it’s always in my mind since he published it. In particular, I will talk about what we should learn in order to fill a gap for a position/job in any technology and my experience.

Which path to choose? I started learning Microsoft (MS) products and then I learned other technologies like Virtualization, Cloud, Storage, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCAP6-DCV Deploy exam experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-10-19-vcap6-dcv-deploy-exam-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 07:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-10-19-vcap6-dcv-deploy-exam-experience/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I am going to talk about my VCAP6-DCV Deploy exam experience.
I thought about making a huge post about the VCAP6-DCV experience (resources, notes, etc.) but, I don’t want to overwhelm you know. Hence, I am going to make another post for that, hence this post will be shorter and more readable.
1st attempt (Java error at the beginning) At September, 21st I sat down to take my first attempt in a VCAP exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCP6-DCV achieved!</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2017-09-03-vcp6-dcv-achieved/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 16:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2017-09-03-vcp6-dcv-achieved/</guid>
      <description>I am going to start talking about the exam VCP6-DCV from VMware. The main resource you should use is the VMware site: http://bit.ly/1PLshWR
There you can check a path to achieve VCP6-DCV (there is a newer version VCP6.5-DCV). I took path 1, as I wasn’t certified.

Later, I took one official training course, VMware vSphere: Install, Configure, Manage [V6].
Next, I passed the vSphere 6 Foundations Exam (2V0-620) months ago and finally I did VMware Certified Professional 6 – Data Center Virtualization Exam (2V0-621).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
