<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows Server on Dan Belmonte</title>
    <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/categories/windows-server/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows Server on Dan Belmonte</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</url>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 09:30:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dangaiden.github.io/categories/windows-server/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WSFC – Validate Configuration wizard error</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-06-29-wsfc-validate-configuration-wizard-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 09:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-06-29-wsfc-validate-configuration-wizard-error/</guid>
      <description>This is a short post talking about Windows Server Failover Clustering (WSFC) and a problem I found when adding the nodes from your cluster using the «Validate a Configuration» wizard.
This wizard is recommended to run after configuring your nodes and before creating the cluster in order to spot any misconfigurations.
So now, let’s go into the problem.
The issue In the wizard when trying to add (in my example) the second node shows an error:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting tips for beginners in Windows Server</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-02-29-troubleshooting-tips-for-beginners-in-windows-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 22:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-02-29-troubleshooting-tips-for-beginners-in-windows-server/</guid>
      <description>I was thinking these days what I wish I have known when I started working with Windows servers, some basic (and some not) commands that can help me to troubleshoot servers without requiring additional software.
That’s why this is a post dedicated to people who just started administering servers with Windows Server 20xx-2019 (I expect at least 2008 although it is going end of support the next month) or maybe you’re curious and want to know more about Windows Server administration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
