<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>vCommunity on Dan Belmonte</title>
    <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/tags/vcommunity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vCommunity on Dan Belmonte</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</url>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 12:50:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dangaiden.github.io/tags/vcommunity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>VMware Explore 2022 local guide</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/vmwareexplore-europe-local-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 12:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/vmwareexplore-europe-local-guide/</guid>
      <description>This is a &amp;ldquo;remake&amp;rdquo; from my previous guide and maybe I have missed something which is not properly updated.
VMworld 2022 Europe is one month away and I am excited because that means the first event that I am going to attend this year (after not being able to attend Kubecon in Valencia&amp;hellip;)
This is a remake of my previous guide with tips about transport, restaurants, places to go, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post VMworld Europe 2019: Days 1 and 2</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-01-31-post-vmworld-europe-2019-days-1-and-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 22:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-01-31-post-vmworld-europe-2019-days-1-and-2/</guid>
      <description>Here I will explain a summary of days 1 and 2 (November 4th and 5th) of VMworld Europe 2019 from my perspective.
So, the first official day is on Monday (November 4th) where there aren’t many people like the next day (the second day, Tuesday 5th) but anyway there are many activities to do!
This time I was awarded a blogger pass, hence, I will have the honor to be with other bloggers at VMworld while enjoying some privileges like having a reserved seat in the general session, stay with other bloggers or join some special events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMworld 2019 Europe local guide</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-14-vmworld-2019-europe-local-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 09:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-14-vmworld-2019-europe-local-guide/</guid>
      <description>VMworld 2019 Europe is almost here! And I made a local guide with tips about transport, restaurants, places to go, etc. to ensure you can enjoy more your experience in VMworld.
General information This event will take place from the 4th (Monday) to 7th (Thursday) of November at Fira Gran Via in Barcelona, Spain.
VMworld is always an amazing opportunity to learn from all the events that will happen there like the Hands-on Lab, Breakout sessions, General sessions, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vFit at VMworld 2019 Europe</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-04-vfit-at-vmworld-2019-europe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 11:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-04-vfit-at-vmworld-2019-europe/</guid>
      <description>Yes! I am happy to announce that the vFit event will happen also at VMworld Europe this year!
Eric Wright (@discoposse) is the creator of this event and you can check how it went at VMworld US here! I love his idea of engaging folks who attend tech events to do some exercise at tech events and why not at VMworld Europe? Enjoy a run with our great community outside VMworld.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
