<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>VMworld Europe on Dan Belmonte</title>
    <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/categories/vmworld-europe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in VMworld Europe on Dan Belmonte</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</url>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 22:51:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dangaiden.github.io/categories/vmworld-europe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Post VMworld Europe 2019: Days 1 and 2</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-01-31-post-vmworld-europe-2019-days-1-and-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 22:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-01-31-post-vmworld-europe-2019-days-1-and-2/</guid>
      <description>Here I will explain a summary of days 1 and 2 (November 4th and 5th) of VMworld Europe 2019 from my perspective.
So, the first official day is on Monday (November 4th) where there aren’t many people like the next day (the second day, Tuesday 5th) but anyway there are many activities to do!

This time I was awarded a blogger pass, hence, I will have the honor to be with other bloggers at VMworld while enjoying some privileges like having a reserved seat in the general session, stay with other bloggers or join some special events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMworld 2019 Europe local guide</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-14-vmworld-2019-europe-local-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 09:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-14-vmworld-2019-europe-local-guide/</guid>
      <description>VMworld 2019 Europe is almost here! And I made a local guide with tips about transport, restaurants, places to go, etc. to ensure you can enjoy more your experience in VMworld.
General information This event will take place from the 4th (Monday) to 7th (Thursday) of November at Fira Gran Via in Barcelona, Spain.
VMworld is always an amazing opportunity to learn from all the events that will happen there like the Hands-on Lab, Breakout sessions, General sessions, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vFit at VMworld 2019 Europe</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-04-vfit-at-vmworld-2019-europe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 11:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2019-10-04-vfit-at-vmworld-2019-europe/</guid>
      <description>Yes! I am happy to announce that the vFit event will happen also at VMworld Europe this year!
Eric Wright (@discoposse) is the creator of this event and you can check how it went at VMworld US here! I love his idea of engaging folks who attend tech events to do some exercise at tech events and why not at VMworld Europe? 
Enjoy a run with our great community outside VMworld.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience at VMworld 2018 Europe – Day 3 and Day 4</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-12-31-vmworld-18-eu-day3-and-day4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 09:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-12-31-vmworld-18-eu-day3-and-day4/</guid>
      <description>To finish these posts about VMworld 2018 Europe, I am going to summarize day 3 and day 4 together as day 4 is usually the less busy of all of them (people usually leave in the morning).
On day 3 (Wednesday), I rest like 5-6 hours (pretty normal to me) after spending some part of the night at the Veeam Party. I made it to be at the enclosure at 8:30 AM because at 9:00 it will start the second general session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience at VMworld 2018 Europe – Day 2</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-12-13-vmworld-18-eu-day2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 09:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-12-13-vmworld-18-eu-day2/</guid>
      <description>Today I am going to explain from my personal experience, the Day 2 at VMworld 2018 Europe, lots of networking, some technical sessions, events and the Solutions Exchange.

Before moving forward, I forgot to mention that I met in my first day a nice guy, Daniel Paluszek @dpaluszek, we had a great conversation and he should be known as the vCloud Director guy ;).
vBreakfast If you don’t what is, check it here: http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre-VMworld 2018 Europe – Expectations and information</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-10-29-pre-vmworld-2018-europe-expectations-and-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 17:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-10-29-pre-vmworld-2018-europe-expectations-and-information/</guid>
      <description>VMworld 2018 Europe is only a week away! And I wanted to explain you share expectations and information I found about. It will be my 1st time!
VMworld Location As you may know, VMworld Europe is located in Fira Barcelona between 5-8th of November. As it’s in Barcelona, I am able to assist without paying any trip (I live close to the city).

Main information  When: 5-8 November 2018</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience at VMworld 2018 Europe – Day 1</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-11-19-vmworld-18-eu-day1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2018-11-19-vmworld-18-eu-day1/</guid>
      <description>Let me talk to you about my experience on my first VMworld! This is a personal experience I want to share about Day 1 at VMworld 2018 Europe.
Introduction I live in Barcelona so, I am fortunate that I don’t need to travel to go to the VMworld Europe. The only thing is to commute by train between home and Fira Barcelona (where VMworld is established). 
It was Monday, November 5th, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
