<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>microsoft on Dan Belmonte</title>
    <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/tags/microsoft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in microsoft on Dan Belmonte</description>
    <image>
      <title>Dan Belmonte</title>
      <url>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</url>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/47</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 22:58:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dangaiden.github.io/tags/microsoft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting tips for beginners in Windows Server</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-02-29-troubleshooting-tips-for-beginners-in-windows-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 22:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/2020-02-29-troubleshooting-tips-for-beginners-in-windows-server/</guid>
      <description>I was thinking these days what I wish I have known when I started working with Windows servers, some basic (and some not) commands that can help me to troubleshoot servers without requiring additional software.
That’s why this is a post dedicated to people who just started administering servers with Windows Server 20xx-2019 (I expect at least 2008 although it is going end of support the next month) or maybe you’re curious and want to know more about Windows Server administration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exam 70-743, Upgrading MCSA Windows Server 2016 experience</title>
      <link>https://dangaiden.github.io/?p=704/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 11:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dangaiden.github.io/?p=704/</guid>
      <description>I will explain quickly my experience regarding the Exam 70-743, Upgrading Your Skills to MCSA: Windows Server 2016 exam from Microsoft I took last April.
It’s been a while since I took an exam from Microsoft (the latest was in 2013 I think) where you probably know that these kind of exams are multiple-choice or single-choice.
Through my career, I saw a lot of people cheating with these exams by memorizing the questions you can find on the internet and finishing it in just 20 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
